twiztv.com 2010-11-22

# TWIZ TV | About Us Section - Privacy Policy

| | |   
**PRIVACY POLICY**  
**Last Updated l** July 22, 2006

TWIZ TV.COM respects your privacy and does take it seriously. We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

All information gathered at this site will be kept strictly confidential. Visitors information such as email or name gathered through optional, voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls, surveys or contests is used for internal purposes only. We do not share your personal information with any third parties, nor do we sell or trade your email address with anyone.

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TWIZ TV.COM. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Cookies are not used on this site. Cookies may, however, be used on one of TWIZ TV's affiliate sites. You may view their privacy statements below: 

* [Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/) \- [Privacy Statement](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/104-9154539-6989561)
* [eBay.com](http://www.ebay.com/) \- [Privacy Statement](http://pages.ebay.com/help/policies/privacy-policy.html)
* [Google.com](http://www.google.com/) \- [Privacy Statement](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)
* [Paypopup.com](http://www.google.com/) \- [Privacy Statement](http://paypopup.com/privacy.php)

Contact us for more information or if you have any concerns. 

|   
---|---|---  
|
